foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
America
foreign
[Music]
Ty and I've got all my people lined up
and they have something really exciting
for us so let's have a look at it
so how's the feeling girls
and what is that you'd like to say to
people back home to your lovely Families
Our Independence Day hair so can I hear
that that whole Spirit of Freedom right
here happy Independence Day dress
John
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Applause]
and I have got a very romantic couple
here with me and let's see what
is store for us
[Music]
and I've got the lovely teens right here
let me tell you they have something
absolutely
here we go
this morning
[Music]
thank you
oh my God
[Music]
well and I'm right here with Mr digvijay
Singh yes
the Basha of up so let's hear it all
from him his experience is still
traveling with the heroes how it has
been over the last six seven days with
him all yours thank you Sangeetha it is
wonderful to you are a part of us from
the day first and it is pleasure having
with you but uh what the best part of
this trip is this we have brought child
from all heroes
all child faces all smiling faces all
all of people are wanting to live this
life
yes yes and they were willing to live
this life but somehow they are not
living and they all this all of a sudden
come out of them and see the faces the
reactions the smiles and it is just
wonderful it is priceless yes it is
priceless and and they remember for they
cherish this moment for a long you know
it might be that uh they will be doing
something they will be doing everything
they are heroes but once the child comes
out of them it is such a wonderful
feeling to share their to see their
feelings
yes all the joy the emotions their
family members even the most important
part of this is this father and parents
who have come come together their their
age their age difference just goes down
it melts down like anything and you
still know and they become friends and
this is the most important thing that I
we have achieved from this trip and it
is such a wonderful to have you all
Travel Clinic and all these Heroes and
really it is a wonderful and one word
um it is
is so you always says
that brings me to the end of this
wonderful wonderful time that I had with
all these lovely people
but I'm saying you know to live happily
ever after is the kind of feeling that I
could see amongst all the heroes right
here so I'm only hoping that they're
going to enjoy all these lovely bites
that we've had together these Great
Moments and memories I will say thank
you all of you thank you Heroes for
being the way you are you really really
made this trip so memorable for all of
us thank you